Guide to the Argus Archives Records
Argus Archives Records
- Organizational Files, 1914, 1932-1994; 1914 1994; 63 linear feet
  - SCAW - Scientists' Center for Animal Welfare: P2- bylaws, P3- correspondence, P4- bibliographies, P5- synopsis of presentation, 1978 - 1983 (Box 1.069, Folder 16)
  - SCC - Society for Cosmetic Chemists: P1- published article, 1976 (Box 1.069, Folder 17)
  - SCHA - Suffolk County Humane Action Group: P1- correspondence, 1976 (Box 1.069, Folder 18)
  - SCL - Save a Cat League: P1- bulletins, P2- newspaper clipping, 1976-1983, undated (Box 1.069, Folder 19)
  - SCOT - Scottish Society for the Prevention of Vivisection (SSPV): P1- leaflets, circa 1948-circa 1972 (Box 1.069, Folder 20)
  - SCOT - Scottish Society for the Prevention of Vivisection (SSPV): P2- correspondence, P3- newsletter, 1973 - 1982 (Box 1.069, Folder 21)
  - SCOT - Scottish Society for the Prevention of Vivisection (SSPV): P4- annual reports, 1973-1974 (Box 1.069, Folder 22)
  - SCOT - Scottish Society for the Prevention of Vivisection (SSPV): P4- annual reports, 1975 - 1976 (Box 1.07, Folder 1)
  - SCOT - Scottish Society for the Prevention of Vivisection (SSPV): P4- annual reports, 1979 - 1980 (Box 1.07, Folder 2)
  - SCOT - Scottish Society for the Prevention of Vivisection (SSPV): P4- annual reports, 1981 - 1982 (Box 1.07, Folder 3)
  - SCW - South Carolina Wildlife and Marine Resources Department: P1- annual report, 1974 - 1975 (Box 1.07, Folder 4)
  - SCW - South Carolina Wildlife and Marine Resources Department: P2- regulations, 1975 - 1980 (Box 1.07, Folder 5)
  - SCX - Sierra Club: P1- bulletins, 1977 - 1983 (Box 1.07, Folder 6)
  - SCX - Sierra Club: P2- correspondence, 1977 - 1980 (Box 1.07, Folder 7)
  - SD - Svenska Diurskyddsföreningen: P1- correspondence, 1975 (Box 1.07, Folder 8)
  - SDES - South Dakota Extension Service: P1- factsheet, circa 1971 (Box 1.07, Folder 9)
  - SDGF - South Dakota Department of Fish, Game and Parks: [P1- printed materials], 1975 - 1980, undated (Box 1.07, Folder 10)
  - SDO - Save the Dolphins: P1- newsletters, 1977-1978 (Box 1.07, Folder 11)
  - SEMA - SEMA Incorporated: P1- newspaper clipping, P2- newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 1.07, Folder 12)
  - SERL - G. D. Searle and Company: P1- newspaper clipping, 1976 (Box 1.07, Folder 13)
  - SF - Salem-Forschungs-institut: P1- bibliography, P2- bulletins, P3- correspondence, circa 1976 (Box 1.07, Folder 14)
  - SFSP- San Francisco Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (SFSPCA): P1- printed matter, 1980 - 1991, undated (Box 1.07, Folder 15)
  - SGRA - Scientists' Group for Reform of Animal Experimentation (SGRAE): P1- bulletins, 1977 - circa 1980 (Box 1.07, Folder 16)
  - SHAC - Smithtown Committee for Humane Animal Control: P1- bulletins, 1977 - 1978 (Box 1.07, Folder 17)
  - SHH - Sweetie, Your Half-Way Home!: P1- newsletter, 1977 (Box 1.07, Folder 18)
  - Society for Humane Legislation: P1- bulletins, 1974 (Box 1.07, Folder 19)
  - SK - Sloan Kettering Institute for Cancer Research: P1- newspaper clippings, 1972-1974 (Box 1.07, Folder 20)
  - SI - Salk Institute: P1- newsletter, P2- bulletins, 1991 - 1992 (Box 1.07, Folder 21)
  - SJAS - Sister Julia's Animal Shelter: P1- newsletter, P2- bulletins, 1989 - 1993 (Box 1.07, Folder 22)
  - SLAD - The Slade Center: P1- booklets, 1981, 1984 (Box 1.07, Folder 23)
  - SLH - St. Luke's Hospital: P1- handwritten notes, circa 1972 (Box 1.07, Folder 24)
  - SMH - St. Mary's Hospital, Research: P1 - handwritten notes, circa 1972 (Box 1.07, Folder 25)
  - SMMI - Sea Mammal Motivational Institute (SEAMAMM): P1- newsletters, 1971-1972 (Box 1.071, Folder 1)
  - SOCE - Society Against Elephant Exploitation: P1- published article, 1977 (Box 1.071, Folder 2)
  - SOS - Save Our Strays: P1- newsletters, circa 1973-1980 (Box 1.071, Folder 3)
  - SOSA - SOS Animals: P1- information kit, 1988 (Box 1.071, Folder 4)
  - SP - Sandanona Pheasantry: P1- bulletins, 1976-1977 (Box 1.071, Folder 5)
  - SPA - Société Protectrice des Animaux: P1- magazines, 1980-1982 (Box 1.071, Folder 6)
  - SPAD - Society for the Protection of Animals in Denmark: P1- bulletin, circa 1981 (Box 1.071, Folder 7)
  - SPAE - Society for the Promotion of Animal Experimentation: P1- bulletins, P2- correspondence, circa 1977 (Box 1.071, Folder 8)
  - SPAR - Sympathetic People for Animal Rights on Earth, Inc. (SPARE): P1- bulletins, 1979-1982 (Box 1.071, Folder 9)
  - SPAY - SPAY/USA: P1- newsletters, 1992-1993 (Box 1.071, Folder 10)
  - SPAY - SPAY/USA: P2- information kit, 1991 (Box 1.071, Folder 11)
  - SPAY - SPAY/USA: P3- bulletins, P4- published articles, P5- correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 1.071, Folder 12)
  - SPBP - Society for the Preservation of Birds of Prey: P1- brochure, 1975 (Box 1.071, Folder 13)
  - SPI - Spira, Henry: P1- published articles, 1976-1989 (Box 1.071, Folder 14)
  - SPI - Spira, Henry: P2- bulletins, P3- correspondence, 1975-1991 (Box 1.071, Folder 15)
  - SPR - Save Pound Animals from Research: P1- bulletins, 1981-1982 (Box 1.071, Folder 16)
  - SQIB - Squibb, E. R. and Sons: P1- handwritten notes, circa 1973 (Box 1.071, Folder 17)
  - SRC - Science Research Council: P1- report, 1979 (Box 1.071, Folder 18)
  - SRI - Southwest Research Institute: P1- correspondence, P2- published article, 1975-1980 (Box 1.071, Folder 19)
  - SS - Science Service: P1- regulations, 1977 (Box 1.071, Folder 20)
  - SSC - Sea Shepherd Conservation Society (SSCS): P1- printed matter, 1982-1991, undated (Box 1.071, Folder 21)
  - SSC - Sea Shepherd Conservation Society (SSCS): P2- report relating to Soviet whaling, 1981 (Box 1.071, Folder 22)
  - SSC - Sea Shepherd Conservation Society (SSCS): P3- correspondence, P4- published articles, 1979 - 1983, 1979-1983, undated (Box 1.071, Folder 23)
  - SSC - Sea Shepherd Conservation Society (SSCS): P5- newspaper clippings, P6- report, 1980-1989, undated (Box 1.071, Folder 24)
  - SSE - Society for the Study of Ethics and Animals (SSEA): P1- correspondence, P2- bulletin, 1982, 1984 (Box 1.071, Folder 25)
  - SSIE - Smithsonian Science Information Exchange: P1- directory of services, 1974 (Box 1.071, Folder 26)
  - SSL - South Shore Analytical and Research Laboratory: P1- typed and handwritten notes, circa 1972-circa 1973 (Box 1.071, Folder 27)
  - SSS - Suncoast Seabird Sanctuary: P1- pamphlet, P2- published article, P3- newspaper clipping, 1980-1981 (Box 1.071, Folder 28)
  - STHS - St. Tammany Humane Society: P1- newsletter, 1979 (Box 1.071, Folder 29)
  - STIS - Scientific and Technical Information Services: P1- brochures, 1975-1976 (Box 1.071, Folder 30)
  - STR - Saskatchewan Tourism and Renewable Resources: P1- guide related to trapping [Saskatchewan Trappers Guide], circa 1979 (Box 1.072, Folder 1)
  - SUP - S.U.P.P.R.E.S.S. - Students United Protesting Research in Sentient Subjects (SUPRESS): P1- correspondence, P2- printed matter, P3- newsletter, 1982 - 1988, circa 1972 (Box 1.072, Folder 2)
  - SVH - St. Vincent's Hospital: P1- handwritten notes, circa 1972 (Box 1.072, Folder 3)
  - SWRI - Sterling-Winthrop Research Institute: P1- published articles, P2- handwritten notes, 1970-circa 1972 (Box 1.072, Folder 4)
  - TC - Tissue Culture Association: AA1- programs, AA2- handwritten notes, circa 1972, 1982 (Box 1.072, Folder 5)
  - TDI - Therapy Days International: P1- newsletters, P2- brochures, P3- correspondence, P4- application for dog registration, 1980-1983, undated (Box 1.072, Folder 6)
  - TF - Thunderbolt Federation: P1- newsletters, P2- bulletins, P3- correspondence, circa 1978 (Box 1.072, Folder 7)
  - THS - Toronto Humane Society: P1- press releases, 1981-1984 (Box 1.072, Folder 8)
  - THS - Toronto Humane Society: P2- magazines, P3- correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 1.072, Folder 9)
  - TPW - Texas Parks and Wildlife Conservation: P1- annual report, 1973-1974 (Box 1.072, Folder 10)
  - TPW - Texas Parks and Wildlife Conservation: P2- regulations, 1979-1980 (Box 1.072, Folder 11)
  - TSU - Trans-Species Unlimited: P1- bulletins, 1983-1991 (Box 1.072, Folder 12)
  - TSU - Trans-Species Unlimited: P1- bulletins, undated (Box 1.072, Folder 13)
  - TSU - Trans-Species Unlimited: P2- pamphlets, 1983-1988, undated (Box 1.072, Folder 14)
  - TSU - Trans-Species Unlimited: P3- leaflets, 1988, undated (Box 1.072, Folder 15)
  - TSU - Trans-Species Unlimited: P4- report relating to rabbit production in China [and information about rabbit breeding industry], 1981-1986 (Box 1.072, Folder 16)
  - TSU - Trans-Species Unlimited: P5- report [and correspondence] relating to barbiturate addiction studies, 1987 (Box 1.072, Folder 17)
  - TSU - Trans-Species Unlimited: P6- correspondence, P7- published articles, P8-newspaper clippings, 1981-1990, undated (Box 1.072, Folder 18)
  - TSU - Trans-Species Unlimited: P8- newspaper clippings, 1988 (Box 1.072, Folder 19)
  - TSU - Trans-Species Unlimited: P9- newsletter [One World], 1981-1984 (Box 1.072, Folder 20)
  - TSU - Trans-Species Unlimited: P10- calendar, P11- poster, 1987, undated (Box 1.072, Folder 21)
  - TWC - Thomas J. Watson Research Center, Yorktown, N.Y.: P1- published articles, 1968 (Box 1.072, Folder 22)
  - TWRA - Tennessee Wildlife Resources Agency: P1- regulations, 1975-1980 (Box 1.072, Folder 23)
  - TWRA - Tennessee Wildlife Resources Agency: P2- thesis [Tennessee Fur Harvest Survey, by Jimmie Z. Warren], 1975 (Box 1.073, Folder 1)
  - TWRA - Tennessee Wildlife Resources Agency: P3- annual reports, 1974-1978 (Box 1.073, Folder 2)
  - UA - Adelphi University: P1- pamphlets, circa 1972-circa 1980 (Box 1.073, Folder 3)
  - UAAR - United Activists for Animal Rights: [P1- printed materials], 1990 (Box 1.073, Folder 4)
  - UAE - Albert Einstein Medical College: P1- handwritten notes, P2- published article, P3- bulletins, circa 1972-1982 (Box 1.073, Folder 5)
  - UAH - U.S. Animal Health Organization: P1: draft of proposed legislation, 1969 (Box 1.073, Folder 6)
  - UAI - Anti-Vivisezionista Italiana (Milan): P1- bulletins, 1979-1983 (Box 1.073, Folder 7)
  - UAI - Anti-Vivisezionista Italiana (Milan): P2- [information booklet], P3- pamphlet, 1979, undated (Box 1.073, Folder 8)
  - UAL - Albany Medical College: P1- handwritten notes, circa 1969 (Box 1.073, Folder 9)
  - UALB - University of Alberta: P1- published article, 1980 (Box 1.073, Folder 10)
  - UAN-USA - United Animal Nations-USA: AA1- bulletins, 1979-1992 (Box 1.073, Folder 11)
  - UB - University of Birmingham, U.K.: P1- published article, circa 1957 (Box 1.073, Folder 12)
  - UBC - Boston College: P1- press releases, 1981 (Box 1.073, Folder 13)
  - UBP - Brooklyn College of Pharmacy: P1- newspaper clippings, P2- handwritten notes, circa 1972, 1976 (Box 1.073, Folder 14)
  - UC - University of Chicago, Ill.: P1- published articles, 1961 (Box 1.073, Folder 15)
  - UCA - Cornell University, N.Y., State College of Agriculture: P1- correspondence, P2- guide to trapping, 1972-1973, 1976 (Box 1.073, Folder 16)
  - UCA - Cornell University, N.Y., State College of Agriculture: P3- report relating to the pet care project, P4- guide to 4-H materials, 1967-circa 1972 (Box 1.073, Folder 17)
  - UCAL - University of Calgary (Alberta, Canada): P1- published article, 1979 (Box 1.073, Folder 18)
  - UCAM - University of Cambridge, U.K.: P1- published article, P2- correspondence, 1971, 1978-1979 (Box 1.073, Folder 19)
  - UCB - University of New York-Brooklyn College: P1- published article, P2- handwritten notes, circa 1972, 1974 (Box 1.073, Folder 20)
  - UCBE - University of California, Berkeley: P1- report, 1988 (Box 1.073, Folder 21)
  - UCBE - University of California, Berkeley: P2- published article, P3- brochures, P4- newspaper clipping, P5- printed matter, 1975-1983 (Box 1.073, Folder 22)
  - UCC - City College of New York (CUNY): P1- handwritten notes, 1972 (Box 1.073, Folder 23)
  - UCCP - Columbia University College of Pharmaceutical Medicine: P1- typed notes, circa 1973 (Box 1.073, Folder 24)
  - UCCS - University of California Sinai Medical Center: P1- published article, 1973 (Box 1.074, Folder 1)
  - UCD - University of California, Davis: P1- newspaper clipping, 1987 (Box 1.074, Folder 2)
  - UCDH - Columbia University, Frances Delafield Hospital: P1- typed notes, circa 1973 (Box 1.074, Folder 3)
  - UCH - City University of New York, Hunter College (CUNY): P1- handwritten notes, circa 1972 (Box 1.074, Folder 4)
  - UCJB - James A. Baker Institute for Animal Health, Cornell University: P1- annual report, 1977 (Box 1.074, Folder 5)
  - UCL - City University of New York, Lehman College (CUNY): P1- handwritten notes, circa 1972 (Box 1.074, Folder 6)
  - UCLA - University of California at Los Angeles: P1- correspondence, 1984 (Box 1.074, Folder 7)
  - UCM - Cornell University, Medical College: P1- typed and handwritten notes, P2- newspaper clipping, P3- published articles, P4- certificate, 1970-1973, 1987 (Box 1.074, Folder 8)
  - UCMI - Carnegie-Mellon University, Mellon Institute: P1- published article, 1971 (Box 1.074, Folder 9)
  - UCMU - Medical University of South Carolina: P1- published article, 1974 (Box 1.074, Folder 10)
  - UCOL: Columbia University: P1- annual report [of research facility], 1977 (Box 1.074, Folder 11)
  - UCP: Columbia University Department of Psychology: P1- correspondence, P2- resume, P3- report relating to animal cognition, P4- report, circa 1983 (Box 1.074, Folder 12)
  - UCP: Columbia University Department of Psychology: P5- draft of proposal, 1983 (Box 1.074, Folder 13)
  - UCP: Columbia University Department of Psychology: P6- published articles, P7- newspaper clipping, 1977-1982 (Box 1.074, Folder 14)
  - UCPS - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons: P1- newsletters, 1981-1982, 1991 (Box 1.074, Folder 15)
  - UCPS - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons: P2- newspaper clippings, P3- correspondence, P4- published articles, P5- certificate, P6- typed and handwritten notes, 1958-1992 (Box 1.074, Folder 16)
  - UCQ - City University of New York, Queens (CUNY): P1- published article, P2- typed and handwritten notes, circa 1973 (Box 1.074, Folder 17)
  - UCR - City University of New York, Richmond College (CUNY): P1- handwritten notes, circa 1972 (Box 1.074, Folder 18)
  - UCRD - Cornell Research Laboratory for Diseases of Dogs: P1- bulletins, 1972-1973 (Box 1.074, Folder 19)
  - UCS - California State College (San Bernardino): P1- report, 1976 (Box 1.074, Folder 20)
  - UCSF - University of California-San Francisco: P1- program, P2- published article, 1975, 1990 (Box 1.074, Folder 21)
  - UCSL - Columbia University School of Law: P1- correspondence, 1975 - 1976 (Box 1.074, Folder 22)
  - UCSV - Colorado State University College of Veterinary Medicine: P1- published article, 1978 (Box 1.074, Folder 23)
  - UCV - Cornell University-New York State Veterinary College, Ithaca: P1- published articles, P2- typed notes, circa 1970, 1973 (Box 1.074, Folder 24)
  - UCWM - Case-Western University School of Medicine: P1- published articles, 1971-1975 (Box 1.074, Folder 25)
  - UCY - City University of New York, York College: P1- handwritten notes, circa 1972 (Box 1.074, Folder 26)
  - UCYR - Syracuse University: P1- certificate, P2- typed and handwritten notes, 1973-1974 (Box 1.074, Folder 27)
  - UDW - Utah Division of Wildlife Resources P1- [rules and regulations], 1975-1980 (Box 1.074, Folder 28)
  - UEW - Eastern Washington State College, Cheney, Washington: P1- report, 1977 (Box 1.074, Folder 29)
  - UEYP - Emory University Primate Research Center: P1- newspaper clippings, 1985 (Box 1.074, Folder 30)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P1 and P2- annual reports, 1966-1969 (Box 1.074, Folder 31)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P1 and P2- annual reports, 1969-1972 (Box 1.074, Folder 32)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P1 and P2- annual reports, 1972-1978 (Box 1.075, Folder 1)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P1 and P2- annual reports, 1978-1983 (Box 1.075, Folder 2)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P1 and P2- annual reports, 1983-1987 (Box 1.075, Folder 3)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P1 and P2- annual reports, 1990-1992 (Box 1.075, Folder 4)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P3- booklet relating to humane killing of animals, P5- booklet relating to use of animals in biomedical research, P6- booklet relating to humane control of wild animals, 1967-1972 (Box 1.075, Folder 5)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P7- booklet relating to welfare of laboratory animals, P8- booklet relating to humane slaughtering, P9- booklet relating to pharmaceutical applications of cell techniques, 1971-1978 (Box 1.075, Folder 6)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P10- booklet relating to management of captive wild animals, 1973 (Box 1.075, Folder 7)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P11- booklet relating to use of animals in toxicological studies, 1969 (Box 1.075, Folder 8)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P12- booklet relating to alternatives to factory farming, 1981 (Box 1.075, Folder 9)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P13- guide to laboratory animal legislation, 1986 (Box 1.075, Folder 10)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P14- correspondence, 1968-1982 (Box 1.075, Folder 11)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P15- newsletters, 1967-1988 (Box 1.075, Folder 12)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P16- printed matter, 1967-1991, undated (Box 1.075, Folder 13)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P17- pamphlets, 1948-1986 (Box 1.075, Folder 14)
  - UFAW - Universities Federation for Animal Welfare: P18- fact sheets, P19- published article, 1964, 1991, undated (Box 1.076, Folder 1)
  - UH - Harvard University: P1- reports [on the U.S. Animal Rights movement], 1982-1983 (Box 1.076, Folder 2)
  - UHK - University of Hawaii Kewalo Basin Marine Research Facility: P1- newspaper clippings, P2- published article, 1977 (Box 1.076, Folder 3)
  - UHM - Harvard University Medical School: P1- newspaper clipping, P2- published article, 1966, 1983 (Box 1.076, Folder 4)
  - UHUM - United Humanitarians: P1- magazine, 1970 (Box 1.076, Folder 5)
  - UIL - University of Illinois: P1- program [newspaper clipping], 1980, 1985 (Box 1.076, Folder 6)
  - UILM - University of Illinois College of Medicine: P1- published article, 1962 (Box 1.076, Folder 7)
  - UIND - University of Indiana School of Dentistry: P1- published article, 1968 (Box 1.076, Folder 8)
  - UIU - University of Illinois, Urbana: P1- report, 1964 (Box 1.076, Folder 9)
  - UIW - Illinois Wesleyan University: P1- published article, 1966 (Box 1.076, Folder 10)
  - UJF - St. John Fisher College: P1- typed notes, circa 1973 (Box 1.076, Folder 11)
  - UKDH - United Kingdom Department of Health and Social Security: P1- report, 1972 (Box 1.076, Folder 12)
  - UKHO - United Kingdom Home Office: P1- annual reports, 1961-1977 (Box 1.076, Folder 13)
  - UKHO - United Kingdom Home Office: P2- report [agriculture committee], 1980 - 1981 (Box 1.076, Folder 14)
  - UKHO - United Kingdom Home Office: P3- report relating to animal experimentation, 1965 (Box 1.076, Folder 15)
  - UKHO - United Kingdom Home Office: P4- statistics, 1977-1981 (Box 1.076, Folder 16)
  - UKHO - United Kingdom Home Office: P5- correspondence, P6- published article, P7- notes, 1971-1983 (Box 1.076, Folder 17)
  - UKLP - United Kingdom Labour Party: P1- charter, 1978 (Box 1.076, Folder 18)
  - ULMA - Louisiana State University and Agricultural and Mechanical College (LSU): P1- brochure, circa 1979 (Box 1.076, Folder 19)
  - UMCM - University of Michigan Medical Center (UM): P1- published article, 1973 (Box 1.076, Folder 20)
  - UMHS - University of Michigan Highway Safety Institute: P1- annual report, 1977 (Box 1.077, Folder 1)
  - UMI - University of Michigan: P1- correspondence, 1979 (Box 1.077, Folder 2)
  - UMIE - University of Michigan Institute for Environmental Quality: P1- report relating to predator control, circa 1971 (Box 1.077, Folder 3)
  - UMN - University of Minnesota: P1- bulletins, P2- report, 1982-1983 (Box 1.077, Folder 4)
  - UMQM - Marquette University Medical School: P1- published articles, 1959, 1964 (Box 1.077, Folder 5)
  - UMSM - University of Mississippi Medical School: P1- published article, 1973 (Box 1.077, Folder 6)
  - UMTM - Mt. Sinai School of Medicine, N.Y.: P1- newspaper clippings, P2- notes, 1974, 1977 (Box 1.077, Folder 7)
  - UN - United Nations: P1- published article, 1977 (Box 1.077, Folder 8)
  - UNA - State University of New York, Albany (SUNY Albany): P1- newspaper clipping, 1977 (Box 1.077, Folder 9)
  - UNBD - State University of New York, Brooklyn ("Downstate")(SUNY Brooklyn): P1- newspaper clipping, 1968 (Box 1.077, Folder 10)
  - UNBI - State University of New York, Binghamton (SUNY Binghamton): P1- typed and handwritten notes, P2- published articles, P3- certificate, 1972-1974 (Box 1.077, Folder 11)
  - UNBR - State University of New York, Brockport (SUNY Brockport): P1- typed and handwritten notes, circa 1972-1973 (Box 1.077, Folder 12)
  - UMBU - State University of New York, Buffalo (SUNY Buffalo): P1- correspondence, P2- typed and handwritten notes, P3- published articles, 1971-1976 (Box 1.077, Folder 13)
  - UNC - North Carolina State University (Raleigh, North Carolina) [NCSU]: P1- correspondence, P2- published article, P3- newspaper clipping, P4- bulletin, 1966, 1980-1984 (Box 1.077, Folder 14)
  - UNC - North Carolina State University (Raleigh, North Carolina) [NCSU]: P5- report [Technology and Animal Rights, by Tom Regan], circa 1976 (Box 1.077, Folder 15)
  - UNM - Northwestern University Medical School: P1- published article, 1964 (Box 1.077, Folder 16)
  - UNST - University of Strathclyde: P1- published article, 1973 (Box 1.077, Folder 17)
  - UNSU - State University of New York, Syracuse ("upstate")(SUNY Syracuse): P1- handwritten notes, P2- published articles, circa 1970-1972 (Box 1.077, Folder 18)
  - UNUS - NYU Students for Animal Rights: P1- newsletter, P2- correspondence, 1977 (Box 1.077, Folder 19)
  - UNYU - New York University: P1- published articles, 1961-1991 (Box 1.077, Folder 20)
  - UNYU - New York University: P2- typed and handwritten notes, P3- correspondence, circa 1968-1974 (Box 1.077, Folder 21)
  - UOK - Oklahoma University: P1- published article, 1972 (Box 1.077, Folder 22)
  - UOMS - University of Oregon Medical School: P1- published article, 1969 (Box 1.077, Folder 23)
  - UOS - Ohio State University (OSU): P1- published articles, 1975-1978 (Box 1.077, Folder 24)
  - UOS - Ohio State University (OSU): P2- draft of report, 1976 (Box 1.077, Folder 25)
  - UOX - Oxford University (Great Britain): P1- published article, 1981 (Box 1.077, Folder 26)
  - UP - Upjohn Company: P1- published articles, 1971-1974 (Box 1.077, Folder 27)
  - UPA - University of Pennsylvania: P1- newspaper clippings, P2- report, 1978-1985 (Box 1.077, Folder 28)
  - UPAC - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Interaction of Animals and Society: P1- program [and letter], 1981-1982 (Box 1.077, Folder 29)
  - UPAH - University of Pennsylvania Head Injury Laboratory: P1- correspondence, P2- transcript of interview, P3- bulletins, 1984-1985 (Box 1.078, Folder 1)
  - UPAH - University of Pennsylvania Head Injury Laboratory: P4- grant application, 1981 (Box 1.078, Folder 2)
  - UPAH - University of Pennsylvania Head Injury Laboratory: P5- published articles, 1974-1984 (Box 1.078, Folder 3)
  - UPAH - University of Pennsylvania Head Injury Laboratory: P6- handwritten notes, undated (Box 1.078, Folder 4)
  - UPAH - University of Pennsylvania Head Injury Laboratory: P7- newspaper clippings, 1984 April-1984 September (Box 1.078, Folder 5)